<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<locationlist>
  <location id="0">
    <name>Asia</name>
    <image>_img/locations/asia.jpg</image>
    <description>Given its size and diversity, the concept of Asia—a name dating back to classical antiquity—may actually have more to do with human geography than physical geography. Asia varies greatly across and within its regions with regard to ethnic groups, cultures, environments, economics, historical ties and government systems.</description>
    <longitude>86.6700</longitude>
    <latitude>46.2830</latitude>
    <travelzone>0</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="1">
    <name>Africa</name>
    <image>_img/locations/africa.jpg</image>
    <description>Algeria is Africa's largest country by area, and Nigeria by population. Africa, particularly central Eastern Africa, is widely accepted as the place of origin of humans and the Hominidae clade (great apes).</description>
    <longitude>21.0936</longitude>
    <latitude>7.1881</latitude>
    <travelzone>1</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="2">
    <name>Antarctica</name>
    <image>_img/locations/antarctica.jpg</image>
    <description>The first formal use of the name "Antarctica" as a continental name in the 1890s is attributed to the Scottish cartographer John George Bartholomew.</description>
    <longitude>0.0000</longitude>
    <latitude>90.0000</latitude>
    <travelzone>2</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="3">
    <name>Australia</name>
    <image>_img/locations/australia.jpg</image>
    <description>After the European discovery of the continent by Dutch explorers in 1606, Australia's eastern half was claimed by Great Britain in 1770 and initially settled through penal transportation to the colony of New South Wales from 26 January 1788.</description>
    <longitude>149.1245</longitude>
    <latitude>35.3080</latitude>
    <travelzone>3</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="4">
    <name>Europe</name>
    <image>_img/locations/europe.jpg</image>
    <description>Europe is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, the Mediterranean Sea to the south, and the Black Sea.</description>
    <longitude>25.3167</longitude>
    <latitude>54.9000</latitude>
    <travelzone>4</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="5">
    <name>North America</name>
    <image>_img/locations/northamerica.jpg</image>
    <description>North America covers an area of about 24,709,000 square kilometers (9,540,000 square miles), about 16.5% of the earth's land area and about 4.8% of its total surface.</description>
    <longitude>100.1667</longitude>
    <latitude>48.1667</latitude>
    <travelzone>5</travelzone>
  </location>
  <location id="6">
    <name>South America</name>
    <image>_img/locations/southamerica.jpg</image>
    <description>Given a long history of colonialism, the overwhelming majority of South Americans speak Portuguese or Spanish</description>
    <longitude>59.4000</longitude>
    <latitude>13.0000</latitude>
    <travelzone>6</travelzone>
  </location>
</locationlist>
